http://www.snaintongolf.co.uk/help-support/privacy-policy

The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.
Privacy Policy
Snainton Golf is committed to ensuring a safe, secure and enjoyable experience for all our users. Therefore, protection of your privacy while browsing or ordering is paramount to us. As per the Data Protection Act 2018, the UK's implementation of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the information we collect from you is done so in a fair, lawful and legal manner. We only collect information about you for 2 simple reasons: firstly, to process your order and secondly, to provide you with the best possible service. You will only receive emails from us with your consent. If at any point you ever wish to opt-out of any promotional and marketing emails from ourselves, you can do so quickly and easily by unsubscribing.
The type of information we will collect about you includes:
Full name
Address
Phone number
Email address
We will never collect sensitive information about you other than the four points outlined above without your explicit consent. If any information we hold appears to be incorrect, you can easily modify this by logging into your account and updating any relevant details. For further assistance with this, please refer to our sales hotline 01723850014.
The personal information which we carry will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) we will always obtain your consent first. We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this from happening if you wish. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.
If you have any questions/comments about privacy, please feel free to email john@snaintongolf.co.uk
Company Details
Snainton Golf is incorporated in England (UK) Company No. 03898371 VAT registration No. 675 4455 06
Klarna
In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain aspects of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you.
General information on Klarna you can find here.Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in Klarna’s privacy policy.
Ordering & Payment
Delivery
Returns
Terms & Conditions
0% Finance
Privacy Policy
About Snainton
Contact Us
Sign up to our golf discount newsletter and get saving!
Sign up
